<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Recent Content on Chimera Arts and Maker Space </title>
      <generator uri="https://hugo.spf13.com">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/index.xml</link>
    
    
    
    <updated>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>Branding Assets</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/assets</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/assets</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Logo&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/static/assets/logo/chimera-logo.png&#34;&gt;PNG file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/static/assets/logo/chimera-logo.psd&#34;&gt;PSD file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/static/assets/logo/chimera-logo.eps&#34;&gt;EPS file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/static/assets/logo/chimera-logo.dwg&#34;&gt;DWG file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Chimera</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Chimera is a community arts and maker space in Sebastopol, California. We&amp;rsquo;re a diverse group of artists, makers, hackers and inventors who share a common desire to create, share and learn from each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Learn More&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/faq/&#34;&gt;FAQ&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Check out our current &lt;a href=&#34;/about/status/&#34;&gt;organization status&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;See what &lt;a href=&#34;/about/equipment/&#34;&gt;tools and equipment&lt;/a&gt; we offer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/mission/&#34;&gt;mission and vision statements&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn about &lt;a href=&#34;/about/history/&#34;&gt;Chimera&amp;rsquo;s history&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;See who is on our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/leadership/&#34;&gt;board and leadership committees&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn about our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/space/&#34;&gt;current space&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/about/teaching/&#34;&gt;Teach at Chimera&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;View our &lt;a href=&#34;/press/&#34;&gt;press page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/assets/&#34;&gt;logo and other assets&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interested in donating? Checkout our &lt;a href=&#34;/donate/&#34;&gt;Donate page&lt;/a&gt; and our &lt;a href=&#34;/wishlist/&#34;&gt;Wishlist&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/faq</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/faq</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Where is Chimera?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re located in downtown Sebastopol, California, an hour north of San Francisco. &lt;a href=&#34;/about/&#34;&gt;Learn more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;What tools and equipment does Chimera have?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Head over to our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/equipment/&#34;&gt;tools and equipment&lt;/a&gt; page to learn about what we have to offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;How do you pronounce Chimera?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;embed video-player&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe 
    class=&#34;youtube-player&#34; 
    type=&#34;text/html&#34; 
    width=&#34;100%&#34; 
    height=&#34;400&#34; 
    src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/HNagWRD96Wg&#34; 
    allowfullscreen 
    frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chimera&#39;s History</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/history</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/history</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Founding &amp;amp; Early Days&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera was founded in early 2012 by &lt;a href=&#34;/about/leadership/&#34;&gt;Dana Woodman&lt;/a&gt; and a small group of people who had a vision for Sonoma County and what it could become. We founded Chimera both as a space to create and a hub for the creative community in this area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the first few months of our history, we grew our community from a few friends to a group of over 800 people. &lt;em&gt;We quickly realized that Sonoma County and the North Bay was craving a space like Chimera&lt;/em&gt;, so we set making the dream a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Ford Garage&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After searching for a space, the Chimera founders settled on the old Ford Garage building in downtown Sebastopol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our initial momentum slowed when the realities of the space we had chosen became clear. The City of Sebastopol required us to install fire sprinklers and emergency access doors into our main, 5,000 sq.ft. space before opening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily our &lt;em&gt;landlord was a believer in our mission&lt;/em&gt; and decided to undertake the renovations himself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;Today&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We &lt;strong&gt;opened for membership in December 2013&lt;/strong&gt; after getting our business license and insurance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re operating in our smaller, 700 sq.ft. mini-makerspace in the back lot of the Ford Garage until the main space is ready for us to move in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_3&#34;&gt;Tomorrow&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our story is continually evolving and if we remember, we&amp;rsquo;ll keep this page updated as we go!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission and Vision</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/mission</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/mission</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Our Mission&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We aim to provide resources, education and community to creative people in Sonoma County and California’s North Bay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Our Vision&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera Arts &amp;amp; Maker Space brings access to equipment, supplies, space and education for artists, makers, hackers, inventors and creative people of all types. We strive to positively influence the arts and maker communities in Sonoma County, California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera believes that by keeping talented people in the North Bay, Sonoma County will become a more vibrant, modern and competitive region as a whole. We are working to engage with people of all ages to show them new, innovative forms of expression and creation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We give people new, relevant skills and experience for a changing world by encouraging entrepreneurship and innovation in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera is creating a thriving and diverse community of creative people that will have a profound impact on Sonoma County.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Reyes</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/chris-reyes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/chris-reyes</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Professional Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My current career has been in manufacturing test engineering since about 2005.  I&amp;rsquo;ve designed test equipment and currently push 1&amp;rsquo;s and 0&amp;rsquo;s around to run test racks.  I work in the solar energy industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Other Interests&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I invariably balance my bicycle at red lights, enjoy my neighbor&amp;rsquo;s home brew and like watching cats.  (They move so unnaturally!)  On the creative side, I&amp;rsquo;ve made great cat &amp;lsquo;furniture&amp;rsquo;,  stout human furniture and recently a quadruped creature costume that occasionally walks through Sebastopol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;d really like to revive my rusty micro-processor and welding skills.  My next big projects will be Daft Punk helmets and a bamboo bicycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;d really like to connect to creative local people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can &lt;a href=&#34;teenyhermitcrab@gmail.com&#34;&gt;email me here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/press</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/press</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Chimera in the Press&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera&amp;rsquo;s been lucky enough to be featured in a variety of publications, including the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Press Democrat&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;http://santarosa.towns.pressdemocrat.com/2013/12/news/event-spotlight-chimera-creations-carnival/&#34;&gt;article about our Chimera Creations Carnival event&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sonoma Family Life Magazine &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sonomafamilylife.com/chimera-arts-and-maker-space-cms-2156&#34;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sonomafamilylife.com/mod/bizdir/listing_detail.php?start=1&amp;amp;detail&amp;amp;listid=1528&#34;&gt;another article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;North Bay Startup Podcast &lt;a href=&#34;http://northbaystartup.com/podcast/9&#34;&gt;interview with Chimera founder Dana Woodman&lt;/a&gt; and a &lt;a href=&#34;http://northbaystartup.com/podcast/15&#34;&gt;follow up interview&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sonoma County Gazette &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sonomacountygazette.com/cms/pages/sonoma-county-news-article-1453.html&#34;&gt;Sebastappeal article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Member of the Media?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re a member of the media and are interested in writing about Chimera, please &lt;a href=&#34;/contact/&#34;&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;. Also check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/assets/&#34;&gt;asset files&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dana Woodman</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/dana-woodman</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/dana-woodman</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Dana.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started Chimera in early 2012 because I felt a need for a community arts and makerspace in Sonoma County. I had been making art out of my small apartment and was growing frustrated by the lack of space and a dire need for a community of people I could get inspired by. I&amp;rsquo;m always blow away by the talented and passionate people in this area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Professional Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been a software developer since 2004, specializing in web development and front-end design. I can write in a multitude of languages including Ruby, Python, Go, and JavaScript.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also have some experience writing software for interactive projects, including writing the software that runs the Chimera RFID security system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can learn more about me &lt;a href=&#34;http://danawoodman.com&#34;&gt;on my website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Other Interests&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m fascinated by micro electronics (Arduino, Raspberry Pi, etc&amp;hellip;), 3D printing, laser cutting, fabrication (welding, CNC, woodworking) and a ton of other things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve collaborated with &lt;a href=&#34;http://touchfabdesign.com/&#34;&gt;TouchFab&lt;/a&gt; to build an interactive light sculpture called the &lt;a href=&#34;http://cloud.touchfabdesign.com/&#34;&gt;Light Cloud&lt;/a&gt;. It was one of the more challenging and rewarding projects I&amp;rsquo;ve been a part of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;How I Can Help&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve got a project that involves software, I&amp;rsquo;d love to lend a hand or at least give some guidance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to shoot me an email at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:dana@chimeraarts.org&#34;&gt;dana@chimeraarts.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jim Wheaton</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/jim-wheaton</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/jim-wheaton</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jim has worked in the computer software world his whole life. Mostly he concentrates on audio and music applications, having worked as a consultant for many companies and for Yamaha Music Technologies, Mixman Technologies, and most recently, Audible Magic Corp. His own company, Harmonic Systems, Inc. produces software products for fun and profit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He has lived in Sebastopol for 13 years and is an active bass guitarist. He enjoys fixing old instruments and finding new homes for them, as well as inventing gizmos and gadgets. He very happy to have found a group of smart, creative, and friendly folks who call themselves Chimera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can visit his web site: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.harmonicsystems.net&#34;&gt;harmonicsystems.net&lt;/a&gt;, or contact him at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:jim@harmonicsystems.net&#34;&gt;jim@harmonicsystems.net&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Randy Hall</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/randy-hall</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/randy-hall</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A transplant from Silicon Valley, Randy has been into technology his entire life. From his first Apple II Plus, loading games like Ultima II from his super sleek 5.25-inch floppy drive, all the way to working for high-tech giant Intel (when it was still small enough to be called &amp;ldquo;Little Blue&amp;rdquo;) for over 15 years, Randy has seen Silicon Valley come of age, and then some. Along the way he discovered that the Silicon Valley lifestyle was shortening his lifespan, so in 2006 he took the biggest risk of his life and moved to Sonoma County with his family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might ask, &amp;ldquo;what does this have to do with film?&amp;rdquo; to which Randy replies, &amp;ldquo;quiet, I&amp;rsquo;m telling a story here.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite his software engineering background and high-tech pedigree, he recently trained at the &lt;a href=&#34;http://filmschoolsf.com&#34; title=&#34;Soon to be called &#39;Film School SF&#39;&#34;&gt;San Francisco School of Digital Filmmaking&lt;/a&gt; in an intensive 12-month filmmaking program, which, when combined with his decades of South Bay living and deep knowledge of technology, digital marketing, and business, instantly turned the lightbulb on inside his skull. He&amp;rsquo;s now building his &lt;a href=&#34;http://vomproductions.com&#34; title=&#34;VOM Productions&#34;&gt;production company&lt;/a&gt; one client at a time, with a clever blend of storytelling and visual effects. His short documentary &amp;ldquo;Udderly Direct&amp;rdquo; was screened at several film festivals, including the Sebastopol Documentary Film Festival in 2013. He has produced and filmed other award-winning short films in his relatively short film career and is on his way to becoming a producer to be reckoned with. In 2013, back when Chimera was still a toddler, Randy produced and directed a short film for the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.48hourfilm.com/en/santarosa/&#34; title=&#34;Just this little film project thing&#34;&gt;48 Hour Film Project Santa Rosa&lt;/a&gt; along with an all-Sonoma County cast and crew, with the team headquartered at the Chimera Art Space for the weekend of the event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From 2007 to 2012, Randy produced and co-hosted a wine industry-related radio/podcast program called &lt;a href=&#34;http://winebizradio.com&#34;&gt;Wine Biz Radio&lt;/a&gt; along with his best buddies Rick &amp;ldquo;Kaz&amp;rdquo; Kasmier and Christophe &amp;ldquo;X&amp;rdquo; Smith. They have dreams of a reunion tour; but honestly, they need their time apart. Lately, Randy has started a new podcast, much in the same vein as Wine Biz Radio, but about the film industry. He hosts it along with a fine young gentleman in San Francisco named Ben Yennie, with the working title of &amp;ldquo;Film Insight: The Producer Foundry Podcast&amp;rdquo;. Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s something of a mouthful, and they&amp;rsquo;re still working on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When he grows up, Randy wants to be the ultimate Renaissance Man, moving freely between the realms of art, science, philosophy, business, and politics with an ease unknown to mere mortals. But in the meantime, he&amp;rsquo;s down for creating film and other art projects, reawakening the wounded software development child inside him, and hacking on electronics, while learning to build laser cutters and CNC mills and 3D printers, all from scratch (if he has anything to say about it!)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chimera&#39;s Wish List</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/wishlist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/wishlist</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Chimera is in need of the following items to outfit our space. If you have some of the following items, &lt;strong&gt;please post on our&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://groups.google.com/forum/#!forum/chimera-art-space&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;describing what you have&lt;/strong&gt; (and ideally a photo or two).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Cool Toys&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Laser cutter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3D printers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CNC mills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Organizational&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cabinets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Storage containers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Peg boards (and hooks)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Window blinds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;Parts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stepper motors, servos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LEDs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Breadboards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_3&#34;&gt;Tools&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Functional power tools (saws, drills, etc&amp;hellip;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tarps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clamps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_4&#34;&gt;Office / Kitchen&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Office chairs!!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;White boards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cork boards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Projectors (and screens)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Water tower (hot water a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full size refrigerator (clean and working!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_5&#34;&gt;Decorations&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Christmas lights (working ones please!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awesome art!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_6&#34;&gt;Other&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/donate/&#34;&gt;Money!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The answer to the meaning of life (and no, we won&amp;rsquo;t accept 47 as an answer!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_7&#34;&gt;Not in the list?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For items not in the list above, &lt;strong&gt;we require a member to take responsibility for the item&lt;/strong&gt;. The reason we do this is so that we don&amp;rsquo;t end up with a lot of things that aren&amp;rsquo;t used and just take up space and collect dust.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Post your item in our &lt;a href=&#34;https://groups.google.com/forum/#!forum/chimera-art-space&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or reach out to a member who might be interested in taking responsibility for your item.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Current Status</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/status</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/status</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Membership&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-success&#34;&gt;Chimera is currently &lt;strong&gt;open for membership in our mini-makerspace&lt;/strong&gt; in the back lot of the Ford Garage building in downtown Sebastopol.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our main space at Chimera is undergoing construction and should be open in a few months (&lt;em&gt;no, we don&amp;rsquo;t have a specific date yet, sorry!&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn more about our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/space/&#34;&gt;current space&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Fiscal Sponsorship&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera is fiscally sponsored by &lt;a href=&#34;http://sebarts.org/&#34;&gt;Sebastopol Center for the Arts&lt;/a&gt; which is the organization that allows us to accept charitable donations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;Learn More&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn more about &lt;a href=&#34;/membership/&#34;&gt;membership&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn more about &lt;a href=&#34;/about/space/&#34;&gt;our space&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teach at Chimera</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/teaching</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/teaching</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interested in teaching at Chimera?&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;re always looking for talented educators to teach classes at Chimera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some things to know about being a teacher Chimera:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You don&amp;rsquo;t need to have a degree in your area of knowledge (but that&amp;rsquo;s a plus!).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We take a percentage of class proceeds for paid classes. Usually it is &lt;em&gt;50% to you and 50% to the Chimera&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You &lt;em&gt;don&amp;rsquo;t need to be a member to teach a class at Chimera&lt;/em&gt;, although members earn more when teaching.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Members get a discount on classes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Classes are &lt;em&gt;open to the public&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We appreciate references so we can vet you as a teacher.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Classes must be 6 students or less&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in teaching a class, &lt;em&gt;the first step is to post your idea in our &lt;a href=&#34;https://groups.google.com/forum/#!forum/chimera-art-space&#34;&gt;Google Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; to see if members would be interested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Let Us Know&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After you&amp;rsquo;ve read and completed the above, &lt;a href=&#34;/contact/&#34;&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt; with the following information:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Proposed date(s)/time(s)&lt;/strong&gt; for your class (give us alternates in case a date isn&amp;rsquo;t available)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Class fee&lt;/strong&gt; per student (if any)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Materials fee&lt;/strong&gt; (if any)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prerequisites&lt;/strong&gt; for students (if any)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Class description&lt;/strong&gt; (2-3 paragraphs about the class, what will be taught and who the class is relevant to)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Teacher bio&lt;/strong&gt; (why should people trust you as a teacher?)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Age restrictions&lt;/strong&gt; for students (e.g. if it&amp;rsquo;s an adults only class, let us know!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any &lt;strong&gt;photos&lt;/strong&gt; of what students will learn (helps to sell your class)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become a Member</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/membership</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/membership</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Chimera is now open to membership! &lt;strong&gt;Before applying for membership, please read the following&lt;/strong&gt; pages/sections:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/about/status/&#34;&gt;Our current status&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/about/space/&#34;&gt;Our space&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1HLFmj0rFuK1uI5WViTvqVvMNKwryNCidUBK0wHjH_g8/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Our membership agreement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;key reasons to become a member of Chimera&lt;/strong&gt; include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multiple work benches to work on projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;All day access, between 8am and 10pm&lt;/em&gt; using your own RFID keycard&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use our 40mbps wifi and our little kitchenette and our heating and AC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;15% discount on classes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to our growing list of tools and supplies, including:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our awesome jewelry studio (rolling mills, files, saws, dapping and forming tools and much more)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A killer electronics lab (oscilloscopes, power supplies, soldering irons and a whole lot more)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Various other arts, crafts and maker supplies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our large library of books&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access any of our new equipment (we&amp;rsquo;re working on getting 3D printers, a laser cutter, a vinyl cutter and more into the space)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Host your own meetups at Chimera!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;And most importantly, being part of a core group of people who are starting the first community maker space in Sonoma County&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like something you&amp;rsquo;d love to be a part of, please click the button below!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Membership is currently just &lt;strong&gt;$45/month&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&#34;text-center&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://chimera.memberful.com/orders/new?plan=1912&#34; class=&#34;btn btn-primary btn-lg&#34;&gt;Become a member now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen our space yet but are interested in being one of our first members, &lt;a href=&#34;/calendar/&#34;&gt;come to a meetup&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;/contact/&#34;&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt; to setup a tour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Membership FAQ&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;What Equipment Do You Have?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/equipment/&#34;&gt;Equipment page&lt;/a&gt; for an updated list of our equipment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;What Volunteer Commitment Are You Looking For?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don&amp;rsquo;t have a hard requirement on volunteering. We want members to take the initiative to find things that need to be done at Chimera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the trash needs to be taken out, then take it out. If a station is messy, clean it up. If you need a piece of equipment, then help us acquire it. If you want to start doing X at Chimera, then make it happen (as long as it&amp;rsquo;s relatively safe and legal)!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We operate on the honor code; we&amp;rsquo;re not going to track your hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_3&#34;&gt;What Membership Commitment Do You Require?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this time, we don&amp;rsquo;t require any membership commitment though we ask you to give us a heads up if you&amp;rsquo;re going to cancel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_4&#34;&gt;What Is The Cancellation Policy?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can cancel at any time with no penalty. If you cancel within the first 5 days of a new month we will refund your money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;d like to cancel your membership, please &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:info@chimeraarts.org&#34;&gt;email us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_5&#34;&gt;Are There Any Setup Fees&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point, there are no setup fees to become a member. We may decide to change this in the future if we deem it necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_6&#34;&gt;Are There Any Other Fees?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you lose your RFID card, it will cost you $10 to replace it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nancy L.T. Hamilton</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/nancy-lt-hamilton</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/nancy-lt-hamilton</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m Nancy L. T. Hamilton (middle initials stand for Lee Tool or as others will testify, the L. T. stands for “Loose Tongue”) and I am a jeweler, a jewelry designer and an artist.  I create jewelry that I call  “modern romantic”.   My jewelry tells stories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use a variety of different materials in creating my work.  The design dictates the type of material that is used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I create educational videos and content that you can find &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nancylthamilton.com/&#34;&gt;on my website&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/user/nancylthamilton&#34;&gt;my YouTube channel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>