<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Recent Content on Chimera Arts and Maker Space </title>
      <generator uri="https://hugo.spf13.com">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/index.xml</link>
    
    
    
    <updated>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>Branding Assets</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/assets</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/assets</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Logo&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/static/assets/logo/chimera-logo.png&#34;&gt;PNG file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/static/assets/logo/chimera-logo.psd&#34;&gt;PSD file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/static/assets/logo/chimera-logo.eps&#34;&gt;EPS file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/static/assets/logo/chimera-logo.dwg&#34;&gt;DWG file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Current Status</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/status</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/status</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Membership&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-success&#34;&gt;Chimera is currently &lt;strong&gt;open for membership in our mini-makerspace&lt;/strong&gt; in the back lot of the Ford Garage building in downtown Sebastopol.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our main space at Chimera is undergoing construction and should be open in a few months (&lt;em&gt;no, we don&amp;rsquo;t have a specific date yet, sorry!&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn more about our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/space/&#34;&gt;current space&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Fiscal Sponsorship&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera is fiscally sponsored by &lt;a href=&#34;http://sebarts.org/&#34;&gt;Sebastopol Center for the Arts&lt;/a&gt; which is the organization that allows us to accept charitable donations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;Learn More&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn more about &lt;a href=&#34;/membership/&#34;&gt;membership&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn more about &lt;a href=&#34;/about/space/&#34;&gt;our space&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Chimera</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Chimera is a community arts and maker space in Sebastopol, California. We&amp;rsquo;re a diverse group of artists, makers, hackers and inventors who share a common desire to create, share and learn from each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Learn More&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/faq/&#34;&gt;FAQ&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Check out our current &lt;a href=&#34;/about/status/&#34;&gt;organization status&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;See what &lt;a href=&#34;/about/equipment/&#34;&gt;tools and equipment&lt;/a&gt; we offer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/mission/&#34;&gt;mission and vision statements&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn about &lt;a href=&#34;/about/history/&#34;&gt;Chimera&amp;rsquo;s history&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;See who is on our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/leadership/&#34;&gt;board and leadership committees&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn about our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/space/&#34;&gt;current space&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/about/teaching/&#34;&gt;Teach at Chimera&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;View our &lt;a href=&#34;/press/&#34;&gt;press page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/assets/&#34;&gt;logo and other assets&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interested in donating? Checkout our &lt;a href=&#34;/donate/&#34;&gt;Donate page&lt;/a&gt; and our &lt;a href=&#34;/wishlist/&#34;&gt;Wishlist&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lee Vandeveer</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/lee-vandeveer</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/lee-vandeveer</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a painter and educator and the desire to explore new artistic possibilities through community at Chimera.  I taught high school art(all grades)and have a keen desire to create classes for multi-age groups.  I am excited to be a member of such an amazing maker community.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chimera&#39;s Space</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/space</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/space</guid>
      <description>

&lt;figure class=&#34;block-image text-center&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;/static/img/photos/portable-pano.jpg&#34; class=&#34;img-responsive img-thumbnail&#34;&gt;
  
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;text-muted&#34;&gt;Planning session at the mini-makerspace.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Current Space&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera is currently renting a small portable office building that is our space for regular meetups, classes, events, and as of December 2013, membership!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This space is great for anyone doing small arts and crafts, jewelry, software or hardware design or anyone working on a computer or who doesn&amp;rsquo;t require a lot of space to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Curious about what equipment and tools we have?&lt;/strong&gt; Check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/equipment/&#34;&gt;list of equipment&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If this sounds interesting to you, learn more about &lt;a href=&#34;/membership/&#34;&gt;membership&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Future Space&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re in the process of an effort to rent a larger fabrication facility that will serve the needs of members that want to do metalwork and other large/messy forms of art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in getting involved in our planning process, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;https://groups.google.com/forum/#!forum/chimera-art-space&#34;&gt;Google Group&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://eepurl.com/zRv7D&#34;&gt;signup to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nancy L.T. Hamilton</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/nancy-lt-hamilton</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/nancy-lt-hamilton</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m Nancy L. T. Hamilton (middle initials stand for Lee Tool or as others will testify, the L. T. stands for “Loose Tongue”) and I am a jeweler, a jewelry designer and an artist.  I create jewelry that I call  “modern romantic”.   My jewelry tells stories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use a variety of different materials in creating my work.  The design dictates the type of material that is used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I create educational videos and content that you can find &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nancylthamilton.com/&#34;&gt;on my website&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/user/nancylthamilton&#34;&gt;my YouTube channel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission and Vision</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/mission</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/mission</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Our Mission&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We aim to provide resources, education and community to creative people in Sonoma County and California’s North Bay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Our Vision&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera Arts &amp;amp; Maker Space brings access to equipment, supplies, space and education for artists, makers, hackers, inventors and creative people of all types. We strive to positively influence the arts and maker communities in Sonoma County, California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera believes that by keeping talented people in the North Bay, Sonoma County will become a more vibrant, modern and competitive region as a whole. We are working to engage with people of all ages to show them new, innovative forms of expression and creation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We give people new, relevant skills and experience for a changing world by encouraging entrepreneurship and innovation in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera is creating a thriving and diverse community of creative people that will have a profound impact on Sonoma County.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bruce Shapiro</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/bruce-shapiro</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/bruce-shapiro</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Trained for and practiced internal medicine for five years, before discovering what was to become a lifelong obsession with connecting things that move to a computer. My first experiments with stepper motors in 1990 resulted in Eggbot&amp;ndash; a spherical plotter for decorating my kids&amp;rsquo; Easter eggs.  Twenty years later I teamed up with Evil Mad Science Laboratories, which led to its release as an &lt;a href=&#34;http://egg-bot.com/&#34;&gt;open-source project&lt;/a&gt; and popular seller on their site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My continued fascination with motion control branched into art and educational uses&amp;ndash; as artist-in-residence at the Science Museum of Minnesota, 2001-4, I taught classes (kids building and programming their Eggbots) and worked on NSF-funded grants creating exhibits.  During the same period, I began ongoing series of large scale motion control sculptures that have been permanently installed in science centers in the US, Canada, Europe, and  Australia.  More info on both the educational and art sides of my work can be found &lt;a href=&#34;http://taomc.com/&#34;&gt;on my site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most recently, I have discovered (and fallen deeply in love) with makerspaces, starting as a member of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mnmill.org/&#34;&gt;The Mill&lt;/a&gt; in Minneapolis and then as one of the founders of &lt;a href=&#34;http://nordeastmakers.com/&#34;&gt;Nordeast Makers&lt;/a&gt; in St. Paul.  Now that my wife and I have moved out to Sebastopol, I am delighted to find Chimera and its wonderful community&amp;ndash; my hope is to continue both making, teaching and learning here!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equipment and Tools at Chimera</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/equipment</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/equipment</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Chimera has a growing collection of &lt;strong&gt;awesome tools and equipment&lt;/strong&gt; at &lt;a href=&#34;/about/space/&#34;&gt;our space&lt;/a&gt;. Below is an incomplete list:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Fabrication&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3D printers (Lulzbot TAZ)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Benchtop multi-axis CNC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Jewelry&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rolling mill&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dapping and forming tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hand saws&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bench top sander&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Small drill press&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flex shafts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pickle pots&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tons of other tools and supplies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;Electronics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital oscilloscope&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adjustable power supplies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Soldering stations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Breadboards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Heat shrink gun&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Various parts (LEDs, resistors, stepper and servo motors and more)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Test equipment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_3&#34;&gt;Other Things&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photography strobe setup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lots of hand tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drawing and painting supplies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work benches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whiteboards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kitchenette&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Heating/AC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_4&#34;&gt;Have a Donation?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Head over to our &lt;a href=&#34;/donate/&#34;&gt;Donate page&lt;/a&gt; to learn how donations work at Chimera.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get in Touch with Chimera</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/contact</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/contact</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Got Questions?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve got general questions about Chimera, first reach out to members on our &lt;a href=&#34;https://groups.google.com/forum/#!forum/chimera-art-space&#34;&gt;Google Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Our members can answer most common questions about Chimera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to get in touch with &lt;a href=&#34;/about/leadership/&#34;&gt;Chimera administrators&lt;/a&gt;, please email us at: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:info@chimeraarts.org&#34;&gt;info@chimeraarts.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; Please be patient if we don&amp;rsquo;t respond right away, we get lots of email and we are all volunteers!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Have Donations?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;d like to donate equipment, time or money, please head on over to our &lt;a href=&#34;/donate/&#34;&gt;Donate page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;Want to Teach?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in teaching at Chimera, please learn more on our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/teaching/&#34;&gt;Teachers page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_3&#34;&gt;Stay In Touch&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re curious about staying up to date with what&amp;rsquo;s going on at Chimera, &lt;em&gt;sign up to our &lt;a href=&#34;http://eepurl.com/zRv7D&#34;&gt;email newsletter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; to get an email once a month with announcements of new classes/events/meetups as well as news and updates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_4&#34;&gt;Contact Info&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;strong&gt;address&lt;/strong&gt; is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6791 Sebastopol Ave.&lt;br /&gt;
Sebastopol, CA 95472&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;strong&gt;phone number&lt;/strong&gt; is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(707) 861-0278&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;strong&gt;email&lt;/strong&gt; is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:info@chimeraarts.org&#34;&gt;info@chimeraarts.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bryce Dow-Williamson</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/bryce-dow-williamson</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/bryce-dow-williamson</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bryce Dow-Williamson works with community and creativity. Guided by a degree in Sustainable Business from Warren Wilson College, Bryce has been working with Chimera on marketing, community relations and organized the Chimera Creations Carnival in December.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bryce was an integral part of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.metroactive.com/bohemian/07.23.08/music-barnrevival-0830.html&#34;&gt;Boogie Room and Gardens&lt;/a&gt;, a commune and venue in Santa Rosa from 2006-2009. While away at school Bryce &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.carolinahg.com/Carolina-Home-Garden/Winter-2011/Pixels-in-Perpetuity/&#34;&gt;curated art shows&lt;/a&gt;, joined a circus, converted an old army truck into an electric vehicle with the &lt;a href=&#34;http://warren-wilson.edu/blogs/blog/2013/06/19/auto-shop-crew-cranks-it-up-with-electric-truck/&#34;&gt;school&amp;rsquo;s auto shop&lt;/a&gt;, built houses and bamboo bikes in Alabama for a summer, made junk art and learned welding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Down to help with any organization, advertising, art cars, welding or whatever for the good of the group&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Randy Hall</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/randy-hall</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/randy-hall</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A transplant from Silicon Valley, Randy has been into technology his entire life. From his first Apple II Plus, loading games like Ultima II from his super sleek 5.25-inch floppy drive, all the way to working for high-tech giant Intel (when it was still small enough to be called &amp;ldquo;Little Blue&amp;rdquo;) for over 15 years, Randy has seen Silicon Valley come of age, and then some. Along the way he discovered that the Silicon Valley lifestyle was shortening his lifespan, so in 2006 he took the biggest risk of his life and moved to Sonoma County with his family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might ask, &amp;ldquo;what does this have to do with film?&amp;rdquo; to which Randy replies, &amp;ldquo;quiet, I&amp;rsquo;m telling a story here.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite his software engineering background and high-tech pedigree, he recently trained at the &lt;a href=&#34;http://filmschoolsf.com&#34; title=&#34;Soon to be called &#39;Film School SF&#39;&#34;&gt;San Francisco School of Digital Filmmaking&lt;/a&gt; in an intensive 12-month filmmaking program, which, when combined with his decades of South Bay living and deep knowledge of technology, digital marketing, and business, instantly turned the lightbulb on inside his skull. He&amp;rsquo;s now building his &lt;a href=&#34;http://vomproductions.com&#34; title=&#34;VOM Productions&#34;&gt;production company&lt;/a&gt; one client at a time, with a clever blend of storytelling and visual effects. His short documentary &amp;ldquo;Udderly Direct&amp;rdquo; was screened at several film festivals, including the Sebastopol Documentary Film Festival in 2013. He has produced and filmed other award-winning short films in his relatively short film career and is on his way to becoming a producer to be reckoned with. In 2013, back when Chimera was still a toddler, Randy produced and directed a short film for the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.48hourfilm.com/en/santarosa/&#34; title=&#34;Just this little film project thing&#34;&gt;48 Hour Film Project Santa Rosa&lt;/a&gt; along with an all-Sonoma County cast and crew, with the team headquartered at the Chimera Art Space for the weekend of the event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From 2007 to 2012, Randy produced and co-hosted a wine industry-related radio/podcast program called &lt;a href=&#34;http://winebizradio.com&#34;&gt;Wine Biz Radio&lt;/a&gt; along with his best buddies Rick &amp;ldquo;Kaz&amp;rdquo; Kasmier and Christophe &amp;ldquo;X&amp;rdquo; Smith. They have dreams of a reunion tour; but honestly, they need their time apart. Lately, Randy has started a new podcast, much in the same vein as Wine Biz Radio, but about the film industry. He hosts it along with a fine young gentleman in San Francisco named Ben Yennie, with the working title of &amp;ldquo;Film Insight: The Producer Foundry Podcast&amp;rdquo;. Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s something of a mouthful, and they&amp;rsquo;re still working on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When he grows up, Randy wants to be the ultimate Renaissance Man, moving freely between the realms of art, science, philosophy, business, and politics with an ease unknown to mere mortals. But in the meantime, he&amp;rsquo;s down for creating film and other art projects, reawakening the wounded software development child inside him, and hacking on electronics, while learning to build laser cutters and CNC mills and 3D printers, all from scratch (if he has anything to say about it!)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/faq</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/faq</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Where is Chimera?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re located in downtown Sebastopol, California, an hour north of San Francisco. &lt;a href=&#34;/about/&#34;&gt;Learn more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;What tools and equipment does Chimera have?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Head over to our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/equipment/&#34;&gt;tools and equipment&lt;/a&gt; page to learn about what we have to offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;How do you pronounce Chimera?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;embed video-player&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe 
    class=&#34;youtube-player&#34; 
    type=&#34;text/html&#34; 
    width=&#34;100%&#34; 
    height=&#34;400&#34; 
    src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/HNagWRD96Wg&#34; 
    allowfullscreen 
    frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chimera&#39;s History</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/history</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/history</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Founding &amp;amp; Early Days&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera was founded in early 2012 by &lt;a href=&#34;/about/leadership/&#34;&gt;Dana Woodman&lt;/a&gt; and a small group of people who had a vision for Sonoma County and what it could become. We founded Chimera both as a space to create and a hub for the creative community in this area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the first few months of our history, we grew our community from a few friends to a group of over 800 people. &lt;em&gt;We quickly realized that Sonoma County and the North Bay was craving a space like Chimera&lt;/em&gt;, so we set making the dream a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Ford Garage&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After searching for a space, the Chimera founders settled on the old Ford Garage building in downtown Sebastopol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our initial momentum slowed when the realities of the space we had chosen became clear. The City of Sebastopol required us to install fire sprinklers and emergency access doors into our main, 5,000 sq.ft. space before opening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily our &lt;em&gt;landlord was a believer in our mission&lt;/em&gt; and decided to undertake the renovations himself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;Today&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We &lt;strong&gt;opened for membership in December 2013&lt;/strong&gt; after getting our business license and insurance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re operating in our smaller, 700 sq.ft. mini-makerspace in the back lot of the Ford Garage until the main space is ready for us to move in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_3&#34;&gt;Tomorrow&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our story is continually evolving and if we remember, we&amp;rsquo;ll keep this page updated as we go!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chimera&#39;s Wish List</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/wishlist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/wishlist</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Chimera is in need of the following items to outfit our space. If you have some of the following items, &lt;strong&gt;please post on our&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://groups.google.com/forum/#!forum/chimera-art-space&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;describing what you have&lt;/strong&gt; (and ideally a photo or two).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Cool Toys&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Laser cutter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3D printers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CNC mills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Organizational&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cabinets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Storage containers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Peg boards (and hooks)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Window blinds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;Parts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stepper motors, servos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LEDs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Breadboards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_3&#34;&gt;Tools&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Functional power tools (saws, drills, etc&amp;hellip;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tarps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clamps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_4&#34;&gt;Office / Kitchen&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Office chairs!!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;White boards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cork boards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Projectors (and screens)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Water tower (hot water a plus)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full size refrigerator (clean and working!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_5&#34;&gt;Decorations&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Christmas lights (working ones please!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awesome art!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_6&#34;&gt;Other&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/donate/&#34;&gt;Money!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The answer to the meaning of life (and no, we won&amp;rsquo;t accept 47 as an answer!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_7&#34;&gt;Not in the list?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For items not in the list above, &lt;strong&gt;we require a member to take responsibility for the item&lt;/strong&gt;. The reason we do this is so that we don&amp;rsquo;t end up with a lot of things that aren&amp;rsquo;t used and just take up space and collect dust.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Post your item in our &lt;a href=&#34;https://groups.google.com/forum/#!forum/chimera-art-space&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or reach out to a member who might be interested in taking responsibility for your item.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>