<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Recent Content on Chimera Arts and Maker Space </title>
      <generator uri="https://hugo.spf13.com">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/index.xml</link>
    
    
    
    <updated>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>Branding Assets</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/assets</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/assets</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Logo&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/static/assets/logo/chimera-logo.png&#34;&gt;PNG file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/static/assets/logo/chimera-logo.psd&#34;&gt;PSD file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/static/assets/logo/chimera-logo.eps&#34;&gt;EPS file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/static/assets/logo/chimera-logo.dwg&#34;&gt;DWG file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Chimera</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Chimera is a community arts and maker space in Sebastopol, California. We&amp;rsquo;re a diverse group of artists, makers, hackers and inventors who share a common desire to create, share and learn from each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Learn More&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/faq/&#34;&gt;FAQ&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Check out our current &lt;a href=&#34;/about/status/&#34;&gt;organization status&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;See what &lt;a href=&#34;/about/equipment/&#34;&gt;tools and equipment&lt;/a&gt; we offer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/mission/&#34;&gt;mission and vision statements&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn about &lt;a href=&#34;/about/history/&#34;&gt;Chimera&amp;rsquo;s history&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;See who is on our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/leadership/&#34;&gt;board and leadership committees&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn about our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/space/&#34;&gt;current space&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/about/teaching/&#34;&gt;Teach at Chimera&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;View our &lt;a href=&#34;/press/&#34;&gt;press page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/assets/&#34;&gt;logo and other assets&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interested in donating? Checkout our &lt;a href=&#34;/donate/&#34;&gt;Donate page&lt;/a&gt; and our &lt;a href=&#34;/wishlist/&#34;&gt;Wishlist&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chimera&#39;s History</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/history</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/history</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Founding &amp;amp; Early Days&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera was founded in early 2012 by &lt;a href=&#34;/about/leadership/&#34;&gt;Dana Woodman&lt;/a&gt; and a small group of people who had a vision for Sonoma County and what it could become. We founded Chimera both as a space to create and a hub for the creative community in this area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the first few months of our history, we grew our community from a few friends to a group of over 800 people. &lt;em&gt;We quickly realized that Sonoma County and the North Bay was craving a space like Chimera&lt;/em&gt;, so we set making the dream a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Ford Garage&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After searching for a space, the Chimera founders settled on the old Ford Garage building in downtown Sebastopol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our initial momentum slowed when the realities of the space we had chosen became clear. The City of Sebastopol required us to install fire sprinklers and emergency access doors into our main, 5,000 sq.ft. space before opening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily our &lt;em&gt;landlord was a believer in our mission&lt;/em&gt; and decided to undertake the renovations himself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;Today&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We &lt;strong&gt;opened for membership in December 2013&lt;/strong&gt; after getting our business license and insurance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re operating in our smaller, 700 sq.ft. mini-makerspace in the back lot of the Ford Garage until the main space is ready for us to move in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_3&#34;&gt;Tomorrow&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our story is continually evolving and if we remember, we&amp;rsquo;ll keep this page updated as we go!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/faq</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/faq</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Where is Chimera?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re located in downtown Sebastopol, California, an hour north of San Francisco. &lt;a href=&#34;/about/&#34;&gt;Learn more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;What tools and equipment does Chimera have?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Head over to our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/equipment/&#34;&gt;tools and equipment&lt;/a&gt; page to learn about what we have to offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;How do you pronounce Chimera?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;embed video-player&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe 
    class=&#34;youtube-player&#34; 
    type=&#34;text/html&#34; 
    width=&#34;100%&#34; 
    height=&#34;400&#34; 
    src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/HNagWRD96Wg&#34; 
    allowfullscreen 
    frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bruce Shapiro</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/bruce-shapiro</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/bruce-shapiro</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Trained for and practiced internal medicine for five years, before discovering what was to become a lifelong obsession with connecting things that move to a computer. My first experiments with stepper motors in 1990 resulted in Eggbot&amp;ndash; a spherical plotter for decorating my kids&amp;rsquo; Easter eggs.  Twenty years later I teamed up with Evil Mad Science Laboratories, which led to its release as an &lt;a href=&#34;http://egg-bot.com/&#34;&gt;open-source project&lt;/a&gt; and popular seller on their site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My continued fascination with motion control branched into art and educational uses&amp;ndash; as artist-in-residence at the Science Museum of Minnesota, 2001-4, I taught classes (kids building and programming their Eggbots) and worked on NSF-funded grants creating exhibits.  During the same period, I began ongoing series of large scale motion control sculptures that have been permanently installed in science centers in the US, Canada, Europe, and  Australia.  More info on both the educational and art sides of my work can be found &lt;a href=&#34;http://taomc.com/&#34;&gt;on my site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most recently, I have discovered (and fallen deeply in love) with makerspaces, starting as a member of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mnmill.org/&#34;&gt;The Mill&lt;/a&gt; in Minneapolis and then as one of the founders of &lt;a href=&#34;http://nordeastmakers.com/&#34;&gt;Nordeast Makers&lt;/a&gt; in St. Paul.  Now that my wife and I have moved out to Sebastopol, I am delighted to find Chimera and its wonderful community&amp;ndash; my hope is to continue both making, teaching and learning here!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bryce Dow-Williamson</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/bryce-dow-williamson</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/bryce-dow-williamson</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bryce Dow-Williamson works with community and creativity. Guided by a degree in Sustainable Business from Warren Wilson College, Bryce has been working with Chimera on marketing, community relations and organized the Chimera Creations Carnival in December.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bryce was an integral part of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.metroactive.com/bohemian/07.23.08/music-barnrevival-0830.html&#34;&gt;Boogie Room and Gardens&lt;/a&gt;, a commune and venue in Santa Rosa from 2006-2009. While away at school Bryce &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.carolinahg.com/Carolina-Home-Garden/Winter-2011/Pixels-in-Perpetuity/&#34;&gt;curated art shows&lt;/a&gt;, joined a circus, converted an old army truck into an electric vehicle with the &lt;a href=&#34;http://warren-wilson.edu/blogs/blog/2013/06/19/auto-shop-crew-cranks-it-up-with-electric-truck/&#34;&gt;school&amp;rsquo;s auto shop&lt;/a&gt;, built houses and bamboo bikes in Alabama for a summer, made junk art and learned welding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Down to help with any organization, advertising, art cars, welding or whatever for the good of the group&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/press</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/press</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Chimera in the Press&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera&amp;rsquo;s been lucky enough to be featured in a variety of publications, including the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Press Democrat&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;http://santarosa.towns.pressdemocrat.com/2013/12/news/event-spotlight-chimera-creations-carnival/&#34;&gt;article about our Chimera Creations Carnival event&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sonoma Family Life Magazine &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sonomafamilylife.com/chimera-arts-and-maker-space-cms-2156&#34;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sonomafamilylife.com/mod/bizdir/listing_detail.php?start=1&amp;amp;detail&amp;amp;listid=1528&#34;&gt;another article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;North Bay Startup Podcast &lt;a href=&#34;http://northbaystartup.com/podcast/9&#34;&gt;interview with Chimera founder Dana Woodman&lt;/a&gt; and a &lt;a href=&#34;http://northbaystartup.com/podcast/15&#34;&gt;follow up interview&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sonoma County Gazette &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sonomacountygazette.com/cms/pages/sonoma-county-news-article-1453.html&#34;&gt;Sebastappeal article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Member of the Media?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re a member of the media and are interested in writing about Chimera, please &lt;a href=&#34;/contact/&#34;&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;. Also check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/assets/&#34;&gt;asset files&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission and Vision</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/mission</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/mission</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Our Mission&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We aim to provide resources, education and community to creative people in Sonoma County and California’s North Bay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Our Vision&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera Arts &amp;amp; Maker Space brings access to equipment, supplies, space and education for artists, makers, hackers, inventors and creative people of all types. We strive to positively influence the arts and maker communities in Sonoma County, California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera believes that by keeping talented people in the North Bay, Sonoma County will become a more vibrant, modern and competitive region as a whole. We are working to engage with people of all ages to show them new, innovative forms of expression and creation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We give people new, relevant skills and experience for a changing world by encouraging entrepreneurship and innovation in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera is creating a thriving and diverse community of creative people that will have a profound impact on Sonoma County.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dana Woodman</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/dana-woodman</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/dana-woodman</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Dana.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started Chimera in early 2012 because I felt a need for a community arts and makerspace in Sonoma County. I had been making art out of my small apartment and was growing frustrated by the lack of space and a dire need for a community of people I could get inspired by. I&amp;rsquo;m always blow away by the talented and passionate people in this area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Professional Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been a software developer since 2004, specializing in web development and front-end design. I can write in a multitude of languages including Ruby, Python, Go, and JavaScript.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also have some experience writing software for interactive projects, including writing the software that runs the Chimera RFID security system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can learn more about me &lt;a href=&#34;http://danawoodman.com&#34;&gt;on my website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Other Interests&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m fascinated by micro electronics (Arduino, Raspberry Pi, etc&amp;hellip;), 3D printing, laser cutting, fabrication (welding, CNC, woodworking) and a ton of other things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve collaborated with &lt;a href=&#34;http://touchfabdesign.com/&#34;&gt;TouchFab&lt;/a&gt; to build an interactive light sculpture called the &lt;a href=&#34;http://cloud.touchfabdesign.com/&#34;&gt;Light Cloud&lt;/a&gt;. It was one of the more challenging and rewarding projects I&amp;rsquo;ve been a part of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;How I Can Help&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve got a project that involves software, I&amp;rsquo;d love to lend a hand or at least give some guidance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to shoot me an email at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:dana@chimeraarts.org&#34;&gt;dana@chimeraarts.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chimera&#39;s Space</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/space</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/space</guid>
      <description>

&lt;figure class=&#34;block-image text-center&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;/static/img/photos/portable-pano.jpg&#34; class=&#34;img-responsive img-thumbnail&#34;&gt;
  
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;text-muted&#34;&gt;Planning session at the mini-makerspace.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Current Space&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chimera is currently renting a small portable office building that is our space for regular meetups, classes, events, and as of December 2013, membership!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This space is great for anyone doing small arts and crafts, jewelry, software or hardware design or anyone working on a computer or who doesn&amp;rsquo;t require a lot of space to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Curious about what equipment and tools we have?&lt;/strong&gt; Check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/equipment/&#34;&gt;list of equipment&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If this sounds interesting to you, learn more about &lt;a href=&#34;/membership/&#34;&gt;membership&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Future Space&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re in the process of an effort to rent a larger fabrication facility that will serve the needs of members that want to do metalwork and other large/messy forms of art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in getting involved in our planning process, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;https://groups.google.com/forum/#!forum/chimera-art-space&#34;&gt;Google Group&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://eepurl.com/zRv7D&#34;&gt;signup to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jim Wheaton</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/jim-wheaton</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/jim-wheaton</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jim has worked in the computer software world his whole life. Mostly he concentrates on audio and music applications, having worked as a consultant for many companies and for Yamaha Music Technologies, Mixman Technologies, and most recently, Audible Magic Corp. His own company, Harmonic Systems, Inc. produces software products for fun and profit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He has lived in Sebastopol for 13 years and is an active bass guitarist. He enjoys fixing old instruments and finding new homes for them, as well as inventing gizmos and gadgets. He very happy to have found a group of smart, creative, and friendly folks who call themselves Chimera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can visit his web site: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.harmonicsystems.net&#34;&gt;harmonicsystems.net&lt;/a&gt;, or contact him at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:jim@harmonicsystems.net&#34;&gt;jim@harmonicsystems.net&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Thompson</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/kyle-thompson</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/kyle-thompson</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kyle Thompson is a metal fabricator who honed his skills in some of the harshest environments and working with the toughest deadlines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kyle has been building custom motorcycles with &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.krausmotorco.com/&#34;&gt;Kraus Motor Company&lt;/a&gt; since 2009.  His work on the Bolide bike helped take home the AMD Championship in 2011, winning 1st place in North America and 3rd place in the world. In further pursuit of his interest in art installation, Kyle joined Burning Man’s &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.burningman.com/on_the_playa/infrastructure/dpw.html&#34;&gt;DPW Metal Shop Crew&lt;/a&gt; in 2012 and helped create a city of 50,000 plus participants and artists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Kyle is not in the desert or at the Kraus Motor Company shop in the redwood forests of Cazadero, he’s at Chimera Art Space working on creating Sonoma County&amp;rsquo;s first ever communal &lt;a href=&#34;http://chimeraarts.org/fab/&#34;&gt;fabrication art facility&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caleb Adam Haye</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/caleb-adam-haye</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/caleb-adam-haye</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Caleb Adam Haye has been developing software professionally since 1997. He now works full time as Principal of Fire, Inc., a software development consulting company based out of the San Francisco Bay Area. Caleb formed Fire in 2005, and since has built web and mobile apps for companies like Google, Apple, Intuit, Netflix, Yahoo!, Visa, Genentech, and Adobe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a former Yahoo! employee, he was the initial member of the Yahoo! Media Innovation Group, pushing the boundaries of rich Internet and client media software on a variety of content delivery platforms. Caleb is a sought after speaker at technology events around the world, and taught as a professor at the Academy of Art Graduate School of New Media. Caleb has worked in some of the world’s most respected research laboratories, including IDEO and Xerox Palo Alto Research Center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can contact Caleb &lt;a href=&#34;http://fire.coop/&#34;&gt;through his website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Reyes</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/chris-reyes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/chris-reyes</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Professional Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My current career has been in manufacturing test engineering since about 2005.  I&amp;rsquo;ve designed test equipment and currently push 1&amp;rsquo;s and 0&amp;rsquo;s around to run test racks.  I work in the solar energy industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Other Interests&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I invariably balance my bicycle at red lights, enjoy my neighbor&amp;rsquo;s home brew and like watching cats.  (They move so unnaturally!)  On the creative side, I&amp;rsquo;ve made great cat &amp;lsquo;furniture&amp;rsquo;,  stout human furniture and recently a quadruped creature costume that occasionally walks through Sebastopol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;d really like to revive my rusty micro-processor and welding skills.  My next big projects will be Daft Punk helmets and a bamboo bicycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;d really like to connect to creative local people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can &lt;a href=&#34;teenyhermitcrab@gmail.com&#34;&gt;email me here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chimera&#39;s Board and Leadership</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/leadership</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/about/leadership</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Our Board&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Oren Slozberg&lt;/strong&gt; - President&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rob Cary&lt;/strong&gt; - Treasurer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/members/dana-woodman/&#34;&gt;Dana Woodman&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Founder, Executive Director&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Terry Beyak&lt;/strong&gt; - Co-Founder, Secretary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spring Maxfield&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Caleb Adam Haye&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Board Bios&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;Oren Slozberg&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oren Slozberg has been working in the field of Education and the Arts for the last 25 years. His specialty areas include youth development theory as well as the use of art to promote critical thinking, aesthetic development and cognitive growth. For the last ten years Slozberg &lt;strong&gt;has been at the helm of Visual Thinking Strategies (VTS), a research-based pedagogy&lt;/strong&gt; that builds cognition, critical thinking, teamwork and language skills through engagement with visual art. Slozberg first served as director of VTS in Northern California, and then for the last seven years as the program&amp;rsquo;s first National Director.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A &lt;strong&gt;non-profit veteran, Slozberg has raised over $10 million, managed several successful non-profit start-ups and scaled up existing programs both programmatically and fiscally&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_3&#34;&gt;Rob Cary&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rob Cary was raised in Ohio and educated in Ohio, Maryland and Michigan. A graduate of Antioch College in Ohio and the University of Michigan, he completed a Smithsonian Fellowship in Maryland, worked as a legislative aide to Maryland State Senator W. Goodman and completed his M.S. in Natural Resource Policy at the University of Michigan. While at U of M, Rob &lt;strong&gt;designed gaming simulations for the UN FAO and USAID on food systems in developing countries&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking for hills with roads that curved, he moved to Sonoma county in 1978. For these past 35 years Rob has had both leadership and ownership positions in the business world as well as serving on various nonprofit boards. From working at Frizelle Enos, to opening up and managing the Real Goods Trading Company store in Santa Rosa and then co-owning Power Service Group, Inc., a company related to energy systems, he has had held many and varied jobs in the business world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the same time, Rob has been equally involved in non-profit community related efforts. Rob &lt;strong&gt;served on the boards of the Community Network, The Bodega Land Trust and the Sebastopol Community Cultural Center&lt;/strong&gt;.  For a short time he was also the Director of the Sebastopol Community Cultural Center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_4&#34;&gt;Caleb Adam Haye&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Caleb Adam Haye has been &lt;strong&gt;developing software professionally since 1997&lt;/strong&gt;. He now works full time as Principal of Fire, Inc., a software development consulting company based out of the San Francisco Bay Area. Caleb formed Fire in 2005, moved the company to Sebastopol in 2008, and since has &lt;strong&gt;built web and mobile apps for companies like Google, Apple, Intuit, Netflix, Yahoo!, Visa, Genentech, and Adobe&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a former Yahoo! employee, he was the initial member of the Yahoo! Media Innovation Group, pushing the boundaries of rich Internet and client media software on a variety of content delivery platforms.  While at Yahoo!, Caleb also was on the winning team for Yahoo&amp;rsquo;s inaugural Hack Day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Caleb is a sought after speaker at technology events around the world, and taught as a professor at the Academy of Art Graduate School of New Media. Caleb has worked with and in some of the worlds most respected research laboratories, including Google Creative Labs, IDEO and Xerox Palo Alto Research Center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_5&#34;&gt;Spring Maxfield&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spring Maxfield is a curator, event planner and avid supporter of all things art. With a background deeply rooted in DIY culture, Spring applies her experience and education in both art history and museum studies to create vibrant community based art projects through various approaches. An art curator for over fifteen years, Spring&amp;rsquo;s work has included shows in underground galleries, wineries as well as established art institutions. She has also worked as a costume designer and seamstress within her local theater community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After years of putting on art events, in 2008 &lt;strong&gt;Spring co-founded The Great Handcar Regatta festival&lt;/strong&gt; which at its peak drew an attendance of up to 18,000 participants. In addition, her innovative organizational skills have been utilized at &lt;strong&gt;events such as Iron Horse Winery&amp;rsquo;s Earth Day Celebration, The Harmony Festival and Maker Faire&lt;/strong&gt;.  Spring&amp;rsquo;s support for the arts also overflows into community involvement and public art projects, where she serves on a number of grassroots, city government and private art foundation committees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spring holds a BA in Art History and Art Practice from Sonoma State University and an MA in Museum Studies from San Francisco State University. When not busy constructing clothing, curating art shows, improving her neighborhood with public art advocacy or riding one of her homemade bicycle contraptions, Spring can be found in the garden at her mini urban homestead with her husband and daughters in Sonoma County, CA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_6&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/members/dana-woodman/&#34;&gt;Dana Woodman&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dana &lt;strong&gt;founded Chimera Art Space in early 2012&lt;/strong&gt; as a place to bring talented, creative and innovative people in the North Bay together. He has worked as a software consultant and serial entrepreneur for nearly a decade, &lt;strong&gt;working with companies including Google and Comcast&lt;/strong&gt; and founding two companies. He studied fine art at the University of the Pacific. He loves traveling, the outdoors and kittens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_7&#34;&gt;Terry Carroll-Beyak&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Terry has been a software developer for two years. He co-founded the software development consultancy firm Teleporter along with Dana Woodman in 2012.  His software career was a dramatic shift from his university education in Environmental Studies at University of California, Santa Cruz. He also &lt;strong&gt;worked on the Obama 08 campaign&lt;/strong&gt;, and interned briefly at two newspapers, the Salinas Californian, and City on a Hill Press. He also &lt;strong&gt;curated and planned TEDxSantaRosa&lt;/strong&gt;, an independently organized event in the style of the TED conference.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>