<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Members on Chimera Arts and Maker Space </title>
      <generator uri="https://hugo.spf13.com">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/index.xml</link>
    
    
    
    <updated>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Reyes</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/chris-reyes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/chris-reyes</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Professional Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My current career has been in manufacturing test engineering since about 2005.  I&amp;rsquo;ve designed test equipment and currently push 1&amp;rsquo;s and 0&amp;rsquo;s around to run test racks.  I work in the solar energy industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Other Interests&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I invariably balance my bicycle at red lights, enjoy my neighbor&amp;rsquo;s home brew and like watching cats.  (They move so unnaturally!)  On the creative side, I&amp;rsquo;ve made great cat &amp;lsquo;furniture&amp;rsquo;,  stout human furniture and recently a quadruped creature costume that occasionally walks through Sebastopol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;d really like to revive my rusty micro-processor and welding skills.  My next big projects will be Daft Punk helmets and a bamboo bicycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;d really like to connect to creative local people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can &lt;a href=&#34;teenyhermitcrab@gmail.com&#34;&gt;email me here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dana Woodman</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/dana-woodman</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/dana-woodman</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Dana.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started Chimera in early 2012 because I felt a need for a community arts and makerspace in Sonoma County. I had been making art out of my small apartment and was growing frustrated by the lack of space and a dire need for a community of people I could get inspired by. I&amp;rsquo;m always blow away by the talented and passionate people in this area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Professional Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been a software developer since 2004, specializing in web development and front-end design. I can write in a multitude of languages including Ruby, Python, Go, and JavaScript.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also have some experience writing software for interactive projects, including writing the software that runs the Chimera RFID security system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can learn more about me &lt;a href=&#34;http://danawoodman.com&#34;&gt;on my website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Other Interests&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m fascinated by micro electronics (Arduino, Raspberry Pi, etc&amp;hellip;), 3D printing, laser cutting, fabrication (welding, CNC, woodworking) and a ton of other things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve collaborated with &lt;a href=&#34;http://touchfabdesign.com/&#34;&gt;TouchFab&lt;/a&gt; to build an interactive light sculpture called the &lt;a href=&#34;http://cloud.touchfabdesign.com/&#34;&gt;Light Cloud&lt;/a&gt;. It was one of the more challenging and rewarding projects I&amp;rsquo;ve been a part of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;How I Can Help&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve got a project that involves software, I&amp;rsquo;d love to lend a hand or at least give some guidance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to shoot me an email at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:dana@chimeraarts.org&#34;&gt;dana@chimeraarts.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jim Wheaton</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/jim-wheaton</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/jim-wheaton</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jim has worked in the computer software world his whole life. Mostly he concentrates on audio and music applications, having worked as a consultant for many companies and for Yamaha Music Technologies, Mixman Technologies, and most recently, Audible Magic Corp. His own company, Harmonic Systems, Inc. produces software products for fun and profit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He has lived in Sebastopol for 13 years and is an active bass guitarist. He enjoys fixing old instruments and finding new homes for them, as well as inventing gizmos and gadgets. He very happy to have found a group of smart, creative, and friendly folks who call themselves Chimera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can visit his web site: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.harmonicsystems.net&#34;&gt;harmonicsystems.net&lt;/a&gt;, or contact him at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:jim@harmonicsystems.net&#34;&gt;jim@harmonicsystems.net&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Randy Hall</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/randy-hall</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/randy-hall</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A transplant from Silicon Valley, Randy has been into technology his entire life. From his first Apple II Plus, loading games like Ultima II from his super sleek 5.25-inch floppy drive, all the way to working for high-tech giant Intel (when it was still small enough to be called &amp;ldquo;Little Blue&amp;rdquo;) for over 15 years, Randy has seen Silicon Valley come of age, and then some. Along the way he discovered that the Silicon Valley lifestyle was shortening his lifespan, so in 2006 he took the biggest risk of his life and moved to Sonoma County with his family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might ask, &amp;ldquo;what does this have to do with film?&amp;rdquo; to which Randy replies, &amp;ldquo;quiet, I&amp;rsquo;m telling a story here.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite his software engineering background and high-tech pedigree, he recently trained at the &lt;a href=&#34;http://filmschoolsf.com&#34; title=&#34;Soon to be called &#39;Film School SF&#39;&#34;&gt;San Francisco School of Digital Filmmaking&lt;/a&gt; in an intensive 12-month filmmaking program, which, when combined with his decades of South Bay living and deep knowledge of technology, digital marketing, and business, instantly turned the lightbulb on inside his skull. He&amp;rsquo;s now building his &lt;a href=&#34;http://vomproductions.com&#34; title=&#34;VOM Productions&#34;&gt;production company&lt;/a&gt; one client at a time, with a clever blend of storytelling and visual effects. His short documentary &amp;ldquo;Udderly Direct&amp;rdquo; was screened at several film festivals, including the Sebastopol Documentary Film Festival in 2013. He has produced and filmed other award-winning short films in his relatively short film career and is on his way to becoming a producer to be reckoned with. In 2013, back when Chimera was still a toddler, Randy produced and directed a short film for the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.48hourfilm.com/en/santarosa/&#34; title=&#34;Just this little film project thing&#34;&gt;48 Hour Film Project Santa Rosa&lt;/a&gt; along with an all-Sonoma County cast and crew, with the team headquartered at the Chimera Art Space for the weekend of the event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From 2007 to 2012, Randy produced and co-hosted a wine industry-related radio/podcast program called &lt;a href=&#34;http://winebizradio.com&#34;&gt;Wine Biz Radio&lt;/a&gt; along with his best buddies Rick &amp;ldquo;Kaz&amp;rdquo; Kasmier and Christophe &amp;ldquo;X&amp;rdquo; Smith. They have dreams of a reunion tour; but honestly, they need their time apart. Lately, Randy has started a new podcast, much in the same vein as Wine Biz Radio, but about the film industry. He hosts it along with a fine young gentleman in San Francisco named Ben Yennie, with the working title of &amp;ldquo;Film Insight: The Producer Foundry Podcast&amp;rdquo;. Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s something of a mouthful, and they&amp;rsquo;re still working on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When he grows up, Randy wants to be the ultimate Renaissance Man, moving freely between the realms of art, science, philosophy, business, and politics with an ease unknown to mere mortals. But in the meantime, he&amp;rsquo;s down for creating film and other art projects, reawakening the wounded software development child inside him, and hacking on electronics, while learning to build laser cutters and CNC mills and 3D printers, all from scratch (if he has anything to say about it!)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nancy L.T. Hamilton</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/nancy-lt-hamilton</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/nancy-lt-hamilton</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m Nancy L. T. Hamilton (middle initials stand for Lee Tool or as others will testify, the L. T. stands for “Loose Tongue”) and I am a jeweler, a jewelry designer and an artist.  I create jewelry that I call  “modern romantic”.   My jewelry tells stories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use a variety of different materials in creating my work.  The design dictates the type of material that is used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I create educational videos and content that you can find &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nancylthamilton.com/&#34;&gt;on my website&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/user/nancylthamilton&#34;&gt;my YouTube channel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bryce Dow-Williamson</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/bryce-dow-williamson</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/bryce-dow-williamson</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bryce Dow-Williamson works with community and creativity. Guided by a degree in Sustainable Business from Warren Wilson College, Bryce has been working with Chimera on marketing, community relations and organized the Chimera Creations Carnival in December.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bryce was an integral part of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.metroactive.com/bohemian/07.23.08/music-barnrevival-0830.html&#34;&gt;Boogie Room and Gardens&lt;/a&gt;, a commune and venue in Santa Rosa from 2006-2009. While away at school Bryce &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.carolinahg.com/Carolina-Home-Garden/Winter-2011/Pixels-in-Perpetuity/&#34;&gt;curated art shows&lt;/a&gt;, joined a circus, converted an old army truck into an electric vehicle with the &lt;a href=&#34;http://warren-wilson.edu/blogs/blog/2013/06/19/auto-shop-crew-cranks-it-up-with-electric-truck/&#34;&gt;school&amp;rsquo;s auto shop&lt;/a&gt;, built houses and bamboo bikes in Alabama for a summer, made junk art and learned welding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Down to help with any organization, advertising, art cars, welding or whatever for the good of the group&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caleb Adam Haye</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/caleb-adam-haye</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/caleb-adam-haye</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Caleb Adam Haye has been developing software professionally since 1997. He now works full time as Principal of Fire, Inc., a software development consulting company based out of the San Francisco Bay Area. Caleb formed Fire in 2005, and since has built web and mobile apps for companies like Google, Apple, Intuit, Netflix, Yahoo!, Visa, Genentech, and Adobe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a former Yahoo! employee, he was the initial member of the Yahoo! Media Innovation Group, pushing the boundaries of rich Internet and client media software on a variety of content delivery platforms. Caleb is a sought after speaker at technology events around the world, and taught as a professor at the Academy of Art Graduate School of New Media. Caleb has worked in some of the world’s most respected research laboratories, including IDEO and Xerox Palo Alto Research Center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can contact Caleb &lt;a href=&#34;http://fire.coop/&#34;&gt;through his website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lee Vandeveer</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/lee-vandeveer</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/lee-vandeveer</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a painter and educator and the desire to explore new artistic possibilities through community at Chimera.  I taught high school art(all grades)and have a keen desire to create classes for multi-age groups.  I am excited to be a member of such an amazing maker community.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Thompson</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/kyle-thompson</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/kyle-thompson</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kyle Thompson is a metal fabricator who honed his skills in some of the harshest environments and working with the toughest deadlines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kyle has been building custom motorcycles with &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.krausmotorco.com/&#34;&gt;Kraus Motor Company&lt;/a&gt; since 2009.  His work on the Bolide bike helped take home the AMD Championship in 2011, winning 1st place in North America and 3rd place in the world. In further pursuit of his interest in art installation, Kyle joined Burning Man’s &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.burningman.com/on_the_playa/infrastructure/dpw.html&#34;&gt;DPW Metal Shop Crew&lt;/a&gt; in 2012 and helped create a city of 50,000 plus participants and artists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Kyle is not in the desert or at the Kraus Motor Company shop in the redwood forests of Cazadero, he’s at Chimera Art Space working on creating Sonoma County&amp;rsquo;s first ever communal &lt;a href=&#34;http://chimeraarts.org/fab/&#34;&gt;fabrication art facility&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bruce Shapiro</title>
      <link>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/bruce-shapiro</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chimeraarts.org/members/bruce-shapiro</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Trained for and practiced internal medicine for five years, before discovering what was to become a lifelong obsession with connecting things that move to a computer. My first experiments with stepper motors in 1990 resulted in Eggbot&amp;ndash; a spherical plotter for decorating my kids&amp;rsquo; Easter eggs.  Twenty years later I teamed up with Evil Mad Science Laboratories, which led to its release as an &lt;a href=&#34;http://egg-bot.com/&#34;&gt;open-source project&lt;/a&gt; and popular seller on their site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My continued fascination with motion control branched into art and educational uses&amp;ndash; as artist-in-residence at the Science Museum of Minnesota, 2001-4, I taught classes (kids building and programming their Eggbots) and worked on NSF-funded grants creating exhibits.  During the same period, I began ongoing series of large scale motion control sculptures that have been permanently installed in science centers in the US, Canada, Europe, and  Australia.  More info on both the educational and art sides of my work can be found &lt;a href=&#34;http://taomc.com/&#34;&gt;on my site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most recently, I have discovered (and fallen deeply in love) with makerspaces, starting as a member of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mnmill.org/&#34;&gt;The Mill&lt;/a&gt; in Minneapolis and then as one of the founders of &lt;a href=&#34;http://nordeastmakers.com/&#34;&gt;Nordeast Makers&lt;/a&gt; in St. Paul.  Now that my wife and I have moved out to Sebastopol, I am delighted to find Chimera and its wonderful community&amp;ndash; my hope is to continue both making, teaching and learning here!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>